

House No. N -3494, Block no: 01 Gulshan-e-Iqbal Karachi <u>linkedin.com/in/abdul-haque-/</u> abdulhaquesheikh600@gmail.com

# ABDUL HAQ SHEIKH

Being a **Textile Engineer** all my professional experience related to the Textile Industry.

**Skill Set**: Strong Management Skills, Inspiring Leadership, Solution orientation and ability to stay focused in pressure situations.

Values: Honesty, Dignity, Passion and Hard Work.

**Ambitions**: Establish myself as a true Manager and develop respectful and lasting relationships along the way in the Textile Industry.

With a good background in MA Economics and BSc Textile Engineering, coupled with over twenty years of experience in Textile Industry management and administration, I bring adaptability, dynamism, perseverance, and leadership to the table. Seeking a managerial role to leverage my expertise, ambition, and ability to lead teams effectively. Eager to contribute to a company's success while continuously learning and growing.

#### Experience

## **International Textile Limited**

(Karachi)

Oct 2018 to August 2020 As a "WEAVING MANAGER"

### □ International Textile Limited

(Karachi)

Oct 2002 to Apr 2017

As a "DEPUTY MANAGER WEAVING"

#### □ Nakshbandi Industries Ltd

(Karachi)

Feb 2000 to Sept 2002

As a "WEAVING MANAGER"

## □ Siddiqsons Denim Mills Ltd

(Karachi)

May 1996 to Feb 2000

As a "MANAGER WEAVING"

### □ Nishat Mills Limited

(Bhikhi Sheikhupura) May 1994 to April 1996

As a "Assistant Manager WEAVING"

#### Education

□ MA (Economics)

# **University Of Sindh Jamshoro**

□ **B Sc TEXTLE ENGINEERING** (Textile Weaving)

1988 to 1992

# **National Textile University Faisalabad**.

Confident, Friendly, Flexible, Optimistic and a Team Player.

Personality Traits

**Personal Information** 

Father Name : WAZIR AHMED
Date of Birth : 13 – 03 – 1969

Marital Status : MARRIED
Religion : ISLAM
Nationality : PAKISTANI

C.N.I.C : 42201 –5547827 – 9

Interest & Activities Driving, Writing, Browsing, Sports (Cricket), News, Social Gatherings, Music.

Languages: English – Urdu – Sindhi – Punjabi

Extracurricular: Enrolled in Governor Sindh IT Program (Generative AI)